[
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": " What comes next in the sequence? 2, 6, 12, 20, 30, ?",
        "options": [
            "40",
            "42",
            "36",
            "38"
        ],
        "answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": " What comes next in the pattern? 1, 4, 9, 16, ?",
        "options": [
            "20",
            "24",
            "25",
            "36"
        ],
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": " What comes next? A, C, F, J, O, ?",
        "options": [
            "S",
            "T",
            "U",
            "V"
        ],
        "answer": "V"
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": " A clock shows 3:15. What is the angle between the hour and minute hand ? ",
        "options": [
            "0°",
            "7.5°",
            "30°",
            "45°"
        ],
        "answer": "7.5°"
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "Mary is 16 years old. Her brother is half her age. When Mary is 30, how old will her brother be ?",
        "options": [
            "15",
            "22",
            "28",
            "30"
        ],
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "Which one is an example of application software ?",
        "options": [
            "A) Windows",
            "Ubuntu",
            "MS Excel",
            "BIOS"
        ],
        "answer": "MS Excel"
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "Which storage device has no moving parts ?",
        "options": [
            "HDD",
            "SSD",
            "CD",
            "Floppy Disk"
        ],
        "answer": "SSD"
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": " Hand is to Glove as Foot is to ?",
        "options": [
            "Toe",
            "Sock",
            "Shoe",
            "Boot"
        ],
        "answer": "Sock"
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Which word can be placed in front of these to make new words: light, ___board, ___room, ___line ",
        "options": [
            "Green",
            "White",
            "Class",
            "Back"
        ],
        "answer": "Back"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": " Which word does not belong ?",
        "options": [
            "Triangle",
            "Square",
            "Circle",
            "Rectangle"
        ],
        "answer": "Circle"
    }
]